There were thousands of soldiers
waiting for me to deliver
supplies and weapons.
You really think you're the
guy to step into this?
How badly does the director
want this war funded?
You do everything like we said.
You walk in and out
like you own the place.
(grunts)
(speaking Spanish)
We can't just wait around
for him to kill us.
- What you got in that bag?
- Nothing.
Well. I guess you ain't
no one-hit wonder
after all. is you?
Take that fucking backpack.
(engine revs)
(breathing heavily)
(dogs barking in distance)
(retches)
(Hall and Oates' I Can't
Go For That playing)
(sirens wailing in distance)
(coughs) (horn blares)
♪ Easy. ready.
willing. overtime ♪
♪ Where does it stop?
♪ Where do you dare me
to draw the line? ♪
(groans)
♪ You've got the body.
now you want my soul ♪
♪ Don't even think about it
♪ Say no go
♪ Yeah. I. I-I
♪ I'll do anything
♪ That you want me to
♪ Yeah. I. I-I
♪ Do almost anything
♪ That you want me to. ooh
♪ Yeah. but I can't
go for that ♪
♪ No-o-o. No can do
♪ I can't go for that. no
♪ No can do
♪ I can't go for that.
can't go for that ♪
♪ Can't go for that.
♪ I can go for being
twice as nice ♪
♪ I can go for just repeating
the same old lines ♪
Yo. young blood. they fuck
up your shit already?
I saw you talking to 'em.
You be really careful about
what you saying now.
♪ I. I-I
♪ I'll do anything
Be real easy to set me up.
♪ Want me to. yeah. I-I
You a smooth talker.
but you don't know
shit about business.
You poach customers. you
gonna get blowback.
I imagine your connect ain't
gonna be too happy about that.
Question is. what you
willing to do about it?
♪ I can't go for that. no
♪ No can do
♪ I can't go for that.
can't go for that ♪
(breathing heavily)
Who are they?
Now. why in the fuck
would I tell you that?
Because I'm asking.
Nicely.
I tell you who they are...
Next time I'm buying.
you be real nice to me.
You feel me?
Uh-huh.
Lenny and Ray-Ray.
They hooked up?
Western Tribe.
Ask around. You'll find 'em.
♪ Yeah. but I can't
go for that ♪
Happy hunting. baby.
♪ No can do. I can't
go for that ♪
(door closes)
♪ I can't go for that
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
(jet engines roaring)
(engine turns off)
(scoffs)
I liked the other place better.
- Me. too.
- (chuckles)
Oh. no. that's fine. Yeah.
just go right ahead.
These are decommissioned?
Well. no. I just lifted
'em from the armory.
You think anyone's gonna notice?
(chuckles) They're
decommissioned.
They're on their way to
destruction at Anniston.
How'd you...
I'm gonna redirect a
smaller shipment.
call it an error. and this
batch is just gonna...
It seems like a lot of
work for some guns.
You didn't tell him?
You getting it now. kemosabe?
No deal.
(chuckles) What?
I don't want any weapons that
could be linked back to the U.S.
You have any idea
what I went through
to get these fuckers loose?
I'm sorry that Logan
wasted your time.
Oh. no. man. You're
wasting my fucking time.
Hey. give us a minute. Okay?
A minute.
(chuckles)
This was the only way to
get rocket launchers.
And when some New York Times
reporter comes down there
to write about the conflict.
traces those serial numbers
back to El Toro. and
then to that fuck-wit.
whose name do you think he's
gonna sing to get out of it?
No one's gonna check
the serial numbers.
I did.
Well. how are we gonna
fight the communists
if we don't have any
fucking weapons?
Okay. (Chuckles)
You have a problem with
the serial numbers.
- Yeah. and the crates.
- Okay.
We'll repack them.
Once we get them down there.
I'll have my guys grind
out the numbers.
Problem solved.
(jet engines roaring)
Okay. before we go. you and
I. we get power tools.
We grind the numbers
out ourselves.
Then we take them down.
Just us? Do have any idea
how long that'll take?
(stomping)
Pedro. does Hector have kids?
Told you not to use this shithole.
Fucking ants.
They're everywhere.
Can you focus for once. please?
The only way to keep your
father's eyes off of us
is to kill one of these five.
Make it look like they
took the money and ran.
- So does Hector have a family?
- Yeah. but Hector's a bitch.
(door closes) Father will be
happy to think he did it.
- So he doesn't have kids?
- No. he's got four of them.
They'll all be better
off without him.
(man singing in Spanish)
Ya te dije no families.
Okay. then Ron's out. too.
- Tomás or Enrique?
- Tomás.
- Why not Enrique?
- Because Enrique works security.
Just did six years
for manslaughter.
And Tomás is a delivery boy.
♪♪
That one. (pen scratches)
(sighs)
Just tell us when it's done.
By myself?
Why not? You already
killed someone.
Reason we're in
this fucking spot.
I didn't have a choice. ese.
You don't have one now.
(dog barking)
(children shouting playfully)
♪♪
(man shouting indistinctly)
(dog barking)
♪♪
MARLA: Where my hot comb?
Lorraine. did you take my...
Who took my hot comb?
LORRAINE: Woodpeckers got
like extra-thick heads
for the pecking. - For real?
- 'Sup. y'all?
- Hey. Franklin.
And that's why you a peckerhead.
- 'Sup. man?
- You a peckerhead!
- What's up?
- Oh! Franklin!
- How you doing. honey?
- Hi. Marla.
Oh! (Chuckles)
Ooh. Oh.
Now. who dotted your eye? Hope
you ain't out there scrapping.
No. ma'am.
Just caught an elbow
playing ball.
Oh. you lying.
You shut your mouth. boy.
Now. this one here got
his head on straight.
See. you might learn a
thing or two from him.
- Yeah. a'ight.
- (Laughs)
- Hello.
Yeah. a'ight.
Know about somebody lying. don't you?
Just like your daddy.
You know about that. don't you?
Look like you been
up to some shit.
(TV playing indistinctly)
Where your toys?
Clean up this house!
I'm sick of this house
looking like this.
Hey. that never would've
happened you had me there.
Fuck. Oh. sorry. man. My bad.
(children speaking indistinctly)
I was gonna hit you up
after a couple runs.
once shit got real.
Guess shit pretty real now. huh?
And you got to hand
over all that money?
Shit. I got you.
How you want to handle it?
Thought you might know somebody.
(children chanting indistinctly)
Well. they ain't gonna
work for free. homie.
Yeah.
(power tools whirring)
(loud whir)
(grunts)
Vete a la gran Puta!
It's gonna take forever.
My people are waiting.
We don't have time
for this shit.
The sooner we get the numbers off...
(whirring resumes)
(loudly) ...the sooner I
can vet the customs guy.
sooner we can go!
(telephone rings)
(power tool whirring)
(ring)
Hello.
Uh. speaking.
I'm s... what? When?
Are... you sure?
In... in L.A.?
Uh. no. no. no. Um...
I-I'll take care of it.
Thank you.
(receiver clatters)
(whirring continues)
(loudly) Hey. I got to
take care of something.
I'll be right back.
(whirring stops)
(jet engines roaring)
(car door opens. closes)
(engine starts)
(car departs)
(horn honks in distance)
(siren wailing. dog
barking in distance)
(birds cawing)
♪♪
You a'ight?
Yeah. just headache.
- How much further?
- Right here.
(men shouting indistinctly)
(clattering)
(indistinct shouting continues)
MAN: Beat that ass. (Indistinct
shouting continues)
MAN: He's scared. look.
(men continue shouting
indistinctly) MAN: Beat that ass.
(scuffling. clattering)
MAN: You can't work here. bruh.
- Hey. beat that bitch.
- You trying to run?
- Naw. bring that ass over here.
- MAN: Get him. get him.
- Kill him. J.J.
- What I'm talkin' 'bout.
Hey. lookit. Look at them
run. look at them run.
- You ain't going nowhere.
- Fuck him up. J.J.
- You know it.
I got it. I got it. Ah.
watch it. watch it.
(all shouting indistinctly)
Damn. man.
♪♪
(scoffs) Leon Simmons. huh?
Lil Leon.
I ain't seen you since Wayside.
Kept in solitary for
scrapping with the cholos.
They was always trying me.
Yeah. you try that shit
in Tehachapi. nigga.
they'll eat your ass
for a snack. homie.
(laughter)
Fuck y'all want?
You want to make some ends?
Look. somethin' got took.
and we need to get it back.
- What they take?
- Doesn't matter.
Well. then roll up out of here. nigga.
You up.
Hey.
Who it is done the taking?
Couple hustlers.
Lenny and Ray-Ray.
Lenny drive a Cutlass.
Yeah. Lenny and Ray-Ray.
Some old punk
motherfuckers. man.
Yep.
A'ight. Let's roll.
(video game beeping)
(men resume shouting
indistinctly)
MAN: Uh-huh. there it is. see?
We was just hoping you could
tell us where they at.
Oh. yeah?
You take shotgun. Lil Leon.
Leon's my name.
(chuckles) Yeah. You got it.
(car door opens) Leon.
(video game playing. men
shouting indistinctly)
(engine starts)
JULIA: Hey. (Whispers)
Can you do that one?
Or this? Yes. Can you put that?
(lock clicks. door creaks)
(squeals)
Hey. Hi.
Look at this. look at this.
Hi.
Wow. (Laughs) Hi.
- Oh. my God.
- (babbles)
- He got so big.
- Yeah.
Hey. Wow.
Yeah. I know. It's a good color.
- Hey. buddy.
- Um. I think that this one
is supposed to be us.
(laughs) Yeah.
- He's really talented.
- (laughs)
- How was the flight?
- Oh. long.
(chuckles)
Did you give Mom a hard time?
No. he was great.
He stared out the window.
barely made a sound.
- He slept.
- (babbles)
- Wow.
- Mm-hmm.
- You don't get that from me.
- (chuckles) I know.
But I kept the barf bags
very close by just in case.
I...
(laughs)
Wow.
You look good. Teddy.
I feel good.
- (babbles)
- (laughs)
I'm sorry. uh. you
didn't get my messages.
No. that's... that's my fault.
I've been running around.
Yeah. the rest of my
week was sh-shaping up
to be kind of quiet. Yeah.
It seemed like if we were
ever gonna do this. then I...
Jules. it's wonderful.
Mm.
(laughs)
(sighs) I was trying to get the A.C.
going.
Oh. yeah. it's kind of...
Kind of been on the fritz.
but. uh. it cools off at night.
Actually. there's
this. uh. this park.
This... we should go. Does...
does he like trains?
Of course. You're not busy?
No. nothing that can't wait.
I just...
I thought you said you
were running around crazy.
- No. no. I didn't say "crazy."
- (babbles)
But you're not doing
Iranian traveler debriefs.
What did James tell you?
He said quite a lot without
actually saying anything.
You know...
I suppose that pretty
much says it all.
Uh-huh.
So... what's going
on out here. Teddy?
(brakes squealing)
(engine shuts off)
(dog barking in distance)
They both live here?
Nah. just Lenny up in there.
How you know he got the cash?
Oh. trust me... Lenny
got your shit. homie.
'cause Ray-Ray's a bitch.
(car doors close)
(birds chirping)
Hey. what's the plan?
♪♪
(gun clicks)
A'ight.
♪♪
What the fuck you doing?
(grunts)
Hey. Lenny! Open up
the door. homie!
I got your little bitch out here.
(groans)
(pounds on door) Hey. Lenny!
Man. what bitch you talking...
(clattering) Uhh!
- Get your ass down.
- Close the door.
Grab that extension cord. homie.
(door closes)
♪♪
Tie his ass up.
- Fuckin' bitches.
- Stop moving! Put your arm up.
Yeah. just like that. homie.
(chuckles) This little
punk again. huh?
Ah. he's back for more.
Thought we fucked you up before. huh?
(Chuckles)
(shifts gears)
(engine shuts off)
(man shouting in
Spanish in distance)
(rooster crowing in distance)
(door opens)
(parrot caws)
(door closes)
(door latch clicks)
(clattering)
(speaking Spanish)
(chair scrapes floor)
(inhales sharply)
Huh? (Chuckles)
(speaking Spanish)
¿Sí?
- Delicioso.
- (chuckles)
Oh. (Chuckles)
(speaking Spanish)
(laughter)
(clattering)
(humming)
(chuckles)
I smell bitches in here.
(clattering continues)
(laughs)
Sticky fiddling ass nigga.
Fuck wrong with you.
Jheri-curl-looking motherfucker?
(vocalizing)
You HTB?
(continues humming)
(clattering continues)
Y'all to the curb asses
need to the get the
fuck up out of here.
Where's my money. man?
Up your mama's pussy.
(laughs)
Hey. Frank. I can't
find nothing.
'Cause. dumb-ass. I don't keep
no fucking money here... ever.
Oh. look! Fuck this shit!
Hey. you some stupid
Frankenstein humming
motherfucker.
stop eating my shit.
- What you say to me. homie?
- You heard me. motherfucker.
Naw. I don't I can hear
you from way back there.
- Come a little closer then.
- Yeah? Say that shit again.
Fuck you... (grunting)
Fuck me. huh? Mm-hmm.
Keep talking. (tape rips)
Hey. look. Hey. now we
both can hum. homie.
Go say somethin'. Keep hummin'.
Mm-mm. Mm. mm. mm.
Find anything?
Hey. now what it
is we looking for?
Hey. what we talking 'bout. man?
- Just a couple grand.
- How much?
Couple grand. (clattering)
His dumb ass keep his hoes all
over the place. (Door closes)
Them bitches steal
anything. nigga.
But you... Yeah. you
all alone. homie.
You ain't got nobody. huh?
Where the fuck them
ends at. fool?
- (muffled speaking)
- (mocks muffled speech)
Hey. I got another song
you would like. though.
(humming Take Me Out
to the Ball Game)
(taps baseball bat rhythmically)
(continues humming)
Whoa. hold up!
(groans)
Let me holla at him for a sec.
No. talk time is over.
Just bust his ass.
Can't tell us a damn
thing if he dead.
(sighs)
Goddamn. you soft
as baby shit. bro.
Hey. you hear that?
You got some ol'
soft-serve ice cream ass
niggas with you. bro.
(laughs)
I don't see no
cupcake makers. man.
Hey. you don't like me
eating your food. huh?
Fuck your janky-ass food. homie!
Nigga. fuck this shit!
(shouts indistinctly) Nigga.
Fuck this shit!
(glass shattering. clattering)
It ain't got to be like this.
Yeah. homie. Fuck all this shit!
(shattering and clattering)
Janky-ass place. (Laughs)
I'm gonna kill you. nigga.
(grunts)
(coughs) I'll mess all
the stuff in here up!
You want to end up dead. man?
Huh?
- Yeah. "F" me. huh?
- Over what?
A few bills that you
jacked off of me?
I'll fuck all this shit up!
(glass shatters)
Just give it over.
Learn how to clean
your house. fool.
(dog barking in distance)
You see that man?
You next.
Where's my money?
(spits)
(laughs) Yeah.
(dog barking in distance)
(train whistle blows)
TEDDY: It's not that funny.
You don't even like
to take aspirin.
Okay. this doesn't require me
actually taking any cocaine.
I think he's really enjoy this.
Yeah. he... he likes
being in motion.
Teddy...
It's a rich white man's drug.
You know? It's for celebrities
and spoiled kids.
Tell that to the
coroners in Miami.
That's not gonna happen.
Not here. not if I'm
controlling who's buying
and who's selling. you know?
This could turn the
entire tide of the war.
Okay. as a colleague. I can
kind of grasp that rationale.
But it's a little unnerving
that you won't at least
acknowledge how...
crazy this is.
Look. I get the faintest
whiff that something's off.
and I shut it down. walk away.
This... it... it's not even
gonna come back to the agency.
It's not just the agency
I'm worried about.
Okay. it's not gonna
come back to me either.
It's not just you
I'm worried about.
Okay. let's just
say for a moment
this is even possible.
Have you considered what running
something this dangerous
will do to you?
Mentally.
Come on. that...
I'm fine.
I'm in a much better place now.
Yeah. because you've
been laying low.
But what happens when
this thing ramps up?
Which it will. You
don't remember Tehran?
Why do you have to put
yourself in this position?
Because it's important.
'Cause the country's
asking me to do it.
I... I mean. I thought that's
what we were doing here.
Yeah. I guess it is.
(train whistle blowing)
(indistinct conversations)
Go. Go make your call.
It's fine. really. Go.
Uh...
- It'll just take a second.
- Mm-hmm.
He really is getting so big.
(line ringing)
ALEJANDRO: Hello.
Hey. how's it going?
It's gonna take me days if I
have to do all these myself.
Where the hell are you?
Listen. I just need
a little more time.
How much?
I'm not sure. but. uh. I'm
gonna try to get back soon.
Anything else?
Uh. no.
Great.
(receiver clatters)
(dial tone)
(receiver clatters. coin drops)
JULIA: You're doing so good.
Hmm?
(children shouting playfully)
Y'all been here all day. man.
Hey. You ain't find nothin'?
I promise you it's
not up there. homie.
Man. I told you.
He wasn't gonna
give up on nothin'.
Wake up. homie.
Franklin.
(dog barking in distance)
(sighs)
My money's got to be here.
(knock on door) RAY-RAY: Lenny.
(mumbling) Shh. shh.
Come on. let's get it. bruh.
(gun clicks) We're going to Fox Hills
Mall and pick up some Staceys.
Come on. bruh. they
gon' sell out.
You in there? Let's go!
(pounding on door)
Lenny!
This a bitch.
I'm out.
(dog barking in distance)
(gun clicks)
No time for this shit. man.
Move.
Hey. you don't like
my humming. huh?
(screams)
- Hold up.
- Get out my face. bruh!
(screaming) Fuck you
like my humming now?
(whack)
(bat clatters) Breathe. nigga.
(gasps. coughs)
(coughing)
(gasping)
- Stand up. nigga.
- Ohh!
- Where my money at. homie?!
- (groans)
(screams)
- Where the fuck is my money?
- Fuck you!
(screaming)
- Oh. God!
- Shit!
- The fuck you doing?
- Shut the fuck up.
Fuck off of me! (Screams)
Shut your ass up!
- Get the fuck off of me!
- Fuck up. nigga.
Nigga. get off! Aah!
(door slams)
You don't know where
the money at. huh?
This is fucked.
(screams)
You're kidding me.
He's a pinche maricón?
So. is it done?
- No.
- Why not?
- Didn't want to.
- You couldn't take them?
You could have waited till he was alone.
Dije no families.
He's a pinche maricón.
You should have just
taken both of them.
It wasn't right. carajo.
Or maybe I should
just go to my father.
Tell him you killed Max.
Okay.
You want me dead?
- (scoffs)
- Do it right now.
Yeah. you don't think I'll do it?
Ándele.
- You don't think I'll do it?
- Stop it!
Should be Enrique.
No. I told you
Enrique's a killer.
I'll do it. Lucia.
Pero you're both
going to be there.
Watch it happen.
Cuando estás listo.
- Get off me!
- Fuck your shit!
- Shut your ass up.
- Get the fuck off me.
KARVEL: Shut your ass up. nigga.
- Yeah. talk shit now.
- The fuck you doing?
- Shut your ass up.
- The fuck. man?
- Uh-huh.
- What are you doing?
- Get your ass down. yeah.
- What now?
What now? Where the
money at. homie?
Where that money at?
He's killing him. man.
Talk shit now. Say something.
- Get off me. man.
- Fuck me. huh?
(indistinct shouting)
- (screams)
- Say something now.
Shit.
What?
- (screams)
- (grunting)
(metal creaking)
He ain't killing him.
(thumping)
He... He giving it to him.
(grunting)
Say something.
(metal creaking)
(screaming and grunting)
(busy signal)
(receiver dings and clatters)
Not what you were hoping for?
Is he out?
No.
I don't know.
It's been a huge day for him.
He'll be okay.
You should go. Teddy.
No. that's okay. Uh.
hey. you hungry?
There's this great
Mexican place.
No.
I'm telling you you should go.
Go do what it is
that you need to do.
Um. let us stay the night here.
and then we'll be
gone in the morning.
Wait. what?
Uh. what?
You don't have to do this.
- Do what?
- This.
This thing that we do.
where you tell me
what you think I want to hear
instead of telling me the truth.
Okay.
Uh. what's the truth?
That we were stationed
together. and it was...
(sighs)
It was fucking great.
It was romantic and exotic.
and I got pregnant.
And instead of telling
me you weren't ready.
you told me you loved me.
Bec... I do.
I love you. I love both of you.
I know.
And I know that being sent to L.A.
wasn't your choice.
Yeah. that's right. It wasn't my...
choice.
But now you're making a
choice to dig in here
and be a part of something
that I can't support.
Okay. look. I think
that you're making
way more of this than it...
It's gonna be.
Teddy. I think you are
making way too little of it.
Look.
I have money.
I have plenty of support.
We'll be fine. We are fine.
We're fine.
If this is what you need
to do. if this is what
you think the country needs
you to do. Teddy. then do it.
Please. come on. let's...
(sighs)
talk about this when
I get back to D.C.
You want to come back to D.C.?
Come on.
You know where we are.
It's not a bad thing. Teddy.
(sighs)
Hey. buddy.
I love you.
(whispers) Now go to sleep.
Yeah.
Okay.
(whispering) Can I keep this?
Go to sleep.
(door opens)
(floor creaking)
Couple grand. huh?
Karvel. hold up.
That's my money.
(chuckling)
(dog barking in distance)
(engine shuts off)
(door creaks)
(snoring)
(speaking Spanish)
órale.
(snoring continues)
(lighter clicks)
(exhales deeply) Know what?
Maybe you can
stay in the stash house.
watch over everything.
Long as you don't mind the ants.
Why wrestling?
Can't be the money.
I just like it.
(speaks Spanish)
Those luchadores were
my heroes growing up.
What did you think
it was going to be?
Fame?
(chuckles) Ladies.
I thought...
it would make me feel...
good.
And it doesn't?
(tires squealing in distance)
Un carro.
- (lowered voice) Pedro.
- What the fuck?
Shh. Look.
- He's big. that vato.
- Told you he's security.
Okay. look. I'll go to the door.
He'll let me in. I'll make
sure the door's unlocked.
You two go in behind me.
Órale.
(sighs)
Dale.
Just wait till I'm inside.
(opens car door)
Mnh-mnh.
(liquor pours)
So. run it down.
What happened?
(dog barking in distance)
Nothin' that can't be handled.
Y'all gonna save me some?
(beads rattle)
Claudia?
Nah. Somethin' else.
What you need?
I need a gun.
Stop.
You sure about that?
I ain't your fucking mama. man.
You take that gun
out of this house.
you better be ready to use it.
You pull it. you hesitate.
that's your funeral.
And if you make that mistake
and your mama show up here.
wilin' out of her mind...
You can be sure...
she'll know that I wasn't the
one that gave you that piece.
(sighs)
(beads rattle)
(laughter on TV)
(Cissy laughs)
(door creaks open)
(TV continues playing
indistinctly)
(Cissy laughs)
CISSY: Ah!
(TV continues
indistinctly. laughter)
(laughs)
You see. son...
Hey. Where have
you been all day?
Cho's.
Hmm? Oh. it's fine.
Some shelves fell on me.
Oh. my God. Let me see.
It's fine. Just kind of sore.
Well. then you should think
about getting a different job.
Yeah.
Thinking about that.
You sure you're okay?
Just tired.
WOMAN: It just might work.
(Arnold speaking
indistinctly on TV)
This is the good part.
PHILLIP: Jumped off the balcony.
ARNOLD: What'chu
talkin' about. Dad?
(laughing)
I love this.
♪♪
Captions by VITA...
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-